stor-age.co.za 2015-11-04

# Privacy Policy

We at Stor-Age want to make your experience with us as convenient as possible. We are firmly committed to protecting the privacy of our customers and those who make use of Stor-Age services. Stor-Age is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not share, sell, or otherwise distribute the financial or personal information of our customers or those who otherwise provide personal information to sample our products and services, to any other persons or organisations in any way other than what is disclosed in this document.

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for http://www.stor-age.co.za/. If you any have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first [contact us by email](mailto:info@stor-age.co.za). In accordance with COPPA, Stor-Age does not, at any time, knowingly collect information from, or market our products or services to, children under the age of 13.

All financial and personal information collected by Stor-Age is held in the strictest confidentiality. Any information, such as an email address, billing and shipping addresses, and other contact information submitted to us, remains the sole property of Stor-Age. This information is used to help us process such items as service provision, payment and to send registration information to our customers.

There are also instances when Stor-Age will use a "cookie" in order to track website usage. These cookies do not collect personal information and are usually terminated once customers leave the site. These cookies record the time of your visit, the date, the "referring" page that brought you to our site, and the IP address that your ISP has assigned to your computer at the time of your visit. This anonymous information is used to assist us in refining our websites to create a better user experience. 

In some areas of the website, Stor-Age may choose to link to another website. We cannot be responsible for any of the content on these external sites. We are also not responsible for the privacy policies in place on those sites. We would encourage any user to read and understand the privacy policy of any third party website before searching too deeply into that content. 

To further protect the privacy of our customers, access to information by our employees is restricted within the company. Only select employees with an absolute need to use that information, in order to better serve customers, are able to view any personal details submitted. 

From time to time, Stor-Age will request more specific information about our customers. This is done in the form of surveys and is completely voluntary. The information gathered in these surveys helps us determine who our customer base is and what their needs are. By compiling this data we can work to improve customer experiences with the company. 

Personal information provided by customers, or those who sample Stor-Age products or services, is sometimes used to contact individuals regarding new information about our Services. Anyone contacted by us with services/product information can request to be removed from further updates at any time.

Overall, we at Stor-Age try to treat our customers as each one of us would like to be treated. We value our privacy and we value yours, too. It is our goal to make your experience with Stor-Age a safe and positive one.
